<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Relaxed Income</title>
    <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Relaxed Income</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.relaxedincome.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Blueprint to Consistently Create Passive Income</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-blueprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-blueprints/</guid>
      <description>Passive income is an income stream derived from an investment that requires little to no work to maintain. It’s a great way to diversify your income and pursue financial freedom. Here you will find a series of steps to create your very own passive income system.
Create a Plan Set a realistic but also ambitious goal for yourself. Then create a list of steps to get there. Figure out how much you need to save, where you can invest, and what kind of returns you need to meet your goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive income aggressive retirement</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-aggressive-retirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-aggressive-retirement/</guid>
      <description>Leveraging passive income to create an aggressive retirement Retirement today looks much different than it did decades ago. With increasing life expectancies, many people running hobbies as businesses, and the rise of peer-to-peer investing, there are many options to consider on how to fund and support a retirement. Here we will discuss how passive income can be leveraged to create an aggressive retirement, no matter your financial position.
What is passive income?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income for Artists</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-for-artists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-for-artists/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Creative Sources of Passive Income for Artists The arts are a key part of our culture, but creatives often struggle to make a living. With the disruption of the pandemic, many musicians, writers and other artists need to explore more creative ways to monetize their work. Here, we discuss the options available to artists to generate passive income.
Royalties Royalties remain some of the most reliable sources of income for creatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income Ideas for a Nurse</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-as-a-nurse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-as-a-nurse/</guid>
      <description>As a nurse, you may be looking for ways to increase your income and get the most out of your skills and experience. There are a variety of passive income ideas that can help you make money in ways that don&amp;rsquo;t require a lot of extra work. Here are some ways that nurses can generate a passive income.
Buy a Rental Property Investing in rental properties can be a great way to make a passive income from the rental payments received from tenants each month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income Ideas for People on H1B Visas - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-on-h1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-on-h1b/</guid>
      <description>Living and working in the United States on an H1B Visa can be a great opportunity for professional growth, but there are some restrictions when it comes to generating passive income. Here are some creative ideas that can help you generate passive income while on an H1B Visa.
EASY &amp;amp; LOW RISK : Get 1000$/year or 83$ every month using the right Credit Card. Cashback credit cards are a type of credit card that offers cashback rewards for using the card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income Scams to Watch Out For</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-scams-to-watch-out-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-scams-to-watch-out-for/</guid>
      <description>Passive income is a great way to make money, but like any industry, there are unscrupulous people looking to take advantage of unsuspecting individuals. Here are some scams to watch out for when looking for a passive income opportunity.
Get Rich Quick Schemes One of the most common scams are get rich quick schemes. These can come in many forms, but most involve someone promising to give you money effortlessly while requiring you to put up money upfront.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income vs. Non-Passive Income</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-vs-non-passive-income/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-vs-non-passive-income/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to generating a consistent income, there are two types of income sources to consider – passive income and non-passive income. Understanding their differences can help you decide which income source to pursue.
Passive Income Passive income is earned from investments that require very little effort to maintain. Generally, the income is generated regardless of whether the investor puts in a certain amount of time or effort. Examples of passive income include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculator For Age Difference : See Combined Earning years</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/calculator-for-age-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 22:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/calculator-for-age-difference/</guid>
      <description>The topic of age difference in relationships has been debated for a long time. While some people believe that age is just a number, others argue that it can affect a relationship in various ways. In this blog, I will share what I think are the advantages and disadvantages of high age differences in a couple.
Advantages:
Different perspectives: When partners are of different ages, they tend to have different perspectives on life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gas Road Trip Calculator : Gas &amp; Electric : US Version</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/gas-road-trip-calculator-for-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/gas-road-trip-calculator-for-us/</guid>
      <description>A road trip can be an amazing adventure, but it can also be expensive. In order to have a successful and stress-free road trip, it is important to consider all of the costs involved. Here are some costs to consider while planning a road trip:
Gasoline: Gasoline is one of the biggest expenses of a road trip. The cost of gas can vary widely depending on the location and time of year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Dividend Stocks for passive income : Yes, you can earn $1000 without working !</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/best-dividend-stocks-for-passive-income/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/best-dividend-stocks-for-passive-income/</guid>
      <description>Investing in dividend stocks in the S&amp;amp;P 500 can be a great way to generate passive income and build long-term wealth. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover what dividend stocks are, the benefits of investing in them, and how to choose the right dividend stocks in the S&amp;amp;P 500.
What are Dividend Stocks?
Dividend stocks are stocks that pay a portion of their profits to shareholders in the form of dividends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Incomes for 10k or less : Yes, you can earn $1000 without working !</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-incomes-for-10k-or-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-incomes-for-10k-or-less/</guid>
      <description>Passive Incomes for 10K or Less: How to Invest in Treasury Bills and Covered Call ETFs
If you are looking to invest in passive income opportunities that require minimal investment, treasury bills and covered call ETFs are great options to consider. In this article, we will explore these two investment strategies and how you can invest in them with 10K or less.
What are Treasury Bills?
Treasury bills, also known as T-bills, are short-term debt securities issued by the US government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request New Passive Income Calculator</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/request-new-calculators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/request-new-calculators/</guid>
      <description>Please post a comment below if would like me to build a new income calculator.
I will try my best to get it stood up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income Calculator : Yes, this is how I earn $1000 without working !</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-calculator-earn-1000-dollars-every-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-calculator-earn-1000-dollars-every-year/</guid>
      <description>What is Passive Income Passive income refers to income earned without active involvement or ongoing effort on your part. It can provide financial security and stability, but it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that all investment comes with some level of risk.
Start with Credit Cards Credit cards are a popular tool for making purchases, with their convenience and rewards programs being major selling points. However, many credit cards can actually end up costing you more money in interest and fees if you&amp;rsquo;re not careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subsrcibe</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/subsrcibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/subsrcibe/</guid>
      <description>Please subsrcibe to get access to all calculators and get notified when I post new practical tips and calculators that help you earn passive income.
Name Email Subscribe </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to take a moment to express my deepest gratitude for subscribing to my blog. Your decision to join our community of readers means a lot to me, and I am truly honored that you have chosen to stay connected with my work.
As a blogger, I am constantly inspired by my readers, and I am excited to have the opportunity to share my thoughts and ideas with you. Your subscription serves as a reminder that my work is meaningful and valuable, and it motivates me to continue producing high-quality content that resonates with you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
