<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Relaxed Income</title>
    <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Relaxed Income</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 14:22:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.relaxedincome.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Blueprint to Consistently Create Passive Income</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-blueprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-blueprints/</guid>
      <description>A Blueprint to Consistently Create Passive Income Passive income is an income stream derived from an investment that requires little to no work to maintain. It’s a great way to diversify your income and pursue financial freedom. Here you will find a series of steps to create your very own passive income system.
Create a Plan Set a realistic but also ambitious goal for yourself. Then create a list of steps to get there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculator For Age Difference : See Combined Earning years</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/calculator-for-age-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 22:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/calculator-for-age-difference/</guid>
      <description>Calculator For Age Difference
The topic of age difference in relationships has been debated for a long time. While some people believe that age is just a number, others argue that it can affect a relationship in various ways. In this blog, I will share what I think are the advantages and disadvantages of high age differences in a couple.
Advantages:
  Different perspectives: When partners are of different ages, they tend to have different perspectives on life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/thankyou/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 14:22:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/thankyou/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to take a moment to express my deepest gratitude for subscribing to my blog. Your decision to join our community of readers means a lot to me, and I am truly honored that you have chosen to stay connected with my work.
As a blogger, I am constantly inspired by my readers, and I am excited to have the opportunity to share my thoughts and ideas with you. Your subscription serves as a reminder that my work is meaningful and valuable, and it motivates me to continue producing high-quality content that resonates with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gas Road Trip Calculator : Gas &amp; Electric : US Version</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/gas-road-trip-calculator-for-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/gas-road-trip-calculator-for-us/</guid>
      <description>Gas Road Trip Calculator
A road trip can be an amazing adventure, but it can also be expensive. In order to have a successful and stress-free road trip, it is important to consider all of the costs involved. Here are some costs to consider while planning a road trip:
 Gasoline: Gasoline is one of the biggest expenses of a road trip. The cost of gas can vary widely depending on the location and time of year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Dividend Stocks for passive income : Yes, you can earn $1000 without working !</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/best-dividend-stocks-for-passive-income/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/best-dividend-stocks-for-passive-income/</guid>
      <description>Investing in dividend stocks in the S&amp;amp;P 500 can be a great way to generate passive income and build long-term wealth. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover what dividend stocks are, the benefits of investing in them, and how to choose the right dividend stocks in the S&amp;amp;P 500.
What are Dividend Stocks?
Dividend stocks are stocks that pay a portion of their profits to shareholders in the form of dividends. Companies that pay dividends are typically mature, stable companies with a track record of profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Incomes for 10k or less : Yes, you can earn $1000 without working !</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-incomes-for-10k-or-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-incomes-for-10k-or-less/</guid>
      <description>Passive Incomes for 10K or Less: How to Invest in Treasury Bills and Covered Call ETFs
If you are looking to invest in passive income opportunities that require minimal investment, treasury bills and covered call ETFs are great options to consider. In this article, we will explore these two investment strategies and how you can invest in them with 10K or less.
What are Treasury Bills?
Treasury bills, also known as T-bills, are short-term debt securities issued by the US government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request New Passive Income Calculator</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/request-new-calculators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/request-new-calculators/</guid>
      <description>Please post a comment below if would like me to build a new income calculator.
I will try my best to get it stood up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income Calculator : Yes, this is how I earn $1000 without working !</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-calculator-earn-1000-dollars-every-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-calculator-earn-1000-dollars-every-year/</guid>
      <description>What is Passive Income Passive income refers to income earned without active involvement or ongoing effort on your part. It can provide financial security and stability, but it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that all investment comes with some level of risk.
Start with Credit Cards Credit cards are a popular tool for making purchases, with their convenience and rewards programs being major selling points. However, many credit cards can actually end up costing you more money in interest and fees if you&amp;rsquo;re not careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subsrcibe</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/subsrcibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/subsrcibe/</guid>
      <description>Please subsrcibe to get access to all calculators and get notified when I post new practical tips and calculators that help you earn passive income.
var submitted=false;  Name Email Subscribe  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>