<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>passive income on Relaxed Income</title>
    <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/tags/passive-income/</link>
    <description>Recent content in passive income on Relaxed Income</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.relaxedincome.com/tags/passive-income/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Blueprint to Consistently Create Passive Income</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-blueprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-blueprints/</guid>
      <description>A Blueprint to Consistently Create Passive Income Passive income is an income stream derived from an investment that requires little to no work to maintain. It’s a great way to diversify your income and pursue financial freedom. Here you will find a series of steps to create your very own passive income system.
Create a Plan Set a realistic but also ambitious goal for yourself. Then create a list of steps to get there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive income aggressive retirement</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-aggressive-retirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-aggressive-retirement/</guid>
      <description>Leveraging passive income to create an aggressive retirement Retirement today looks much different than it did decades ago. With increasing life expectancies, many people running hobbies as businesses, and the rise of peer-to-peer investing, there are many options to consider on how to fund and support a retirement. Here we will discuss how passive income can be leveraged to create an aggressive retirement, no matter your financial position.
What is passive income?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income Ideas for a Nurse</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-as-a-nurse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-as-a-nurse/</guid>
      <description>Passive Income Ideas for Nurses As a nurse, you may be looking for ways to increase your income and get the most out of your skills and experience. There are a variety of passive income ideas that can help you make money in ways that don&amp;rsquo;t require a lot of extra work. Here are some ways that nurses can generate a passive income.
Buy a Rental Property Investing in rental properties can be a great way to make a passive income from the rental payments received from tenants each month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income Ideas for People on H1B Visas</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-on-h1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-on-h1b/</guid>
      <description>Passive Income Ideas for People on H1B Visas Living and working in the United States on an H1B Visa can be a great opportunity for professional growth, but there are some restrictions when it comes to generating passive income. Here are some creative ideas that can help you generate passive income while on an H1B Visa.
Investing in the Stock Market Investing in the stock market can be a great way to generate passive income, as investing takes relatively little effort and has the potential to generate great returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income Scams to Watch Out For</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-scams-to-watch-out-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-scams-to-watch-out-for/</guid>
      <description>Passive Income Scams to Watch Out For Passive income is a great way to make money, but like any industry, there are unscrupulous people looking to take advantage of unsuspecting individuals. Here are some scams to watch out for when looking for a passive income opportunity.
Get Rich Quick Schemes One of the most common scams are get rich quick schemes. These can come in many forms, but most involve someone promising to give you money effortlessly while requiring you to put up money upfront.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income vs. Non-Passive Income</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-vs-non-passive-income/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/passive-income-vs-non-passive-income/</guid>
      <description>Passive Income vs. Non-Passive Income When it comes to generating a consistent income, there are two types of income sources to consider – passive income and non-passive income. Understanding their differences can help you decide which income source to pursue.
Passive Income Passive income is earned from investments that require very little effort to maintain. Generally, the income is generated regardless of whether the investor puts in a certain amount of time or effort.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>